{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Brick \u0026 Stone Floor Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/40877/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40877,"taskName":"Brick and Stone Driveways \u0026 Floors - Install","taskDescription":"Install Brick or Stone Driveways \u0026 Floors","xmTaskDescriptor":"Brick \u0026 Stone Floor Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":61,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"stone driveway installation brick floor","textMessagingName":"Inst Mason Flatwork","rolloverLongDesc":"Used for driveways \u0026 floors. Does not require extensive vertical forms. Appropriate when building or replacing old mostly-flat concrete structures.","rolloverShortDesc":"Build forms, install bricks, stones, pavers, etc.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install Brick/Stone Floors or Driveways. HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated brick/stone floor contractors in your area.","htmlTitle":"Brick or Stone Floor Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Install Stone or Brick Driveway","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":16,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Brick and Stone Driveways \u0026 Floors - Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Brick and Stone Driveways \u0026 Floors - Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Brick and Stone Project","urlName":"Brick-Stone-Floor-Driveway-Install","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Brick/Stone Floor \u0026 Driveway Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"stone,driveway,installation,brick,floor","emcCategoryOid":-12008,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":1435,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40877/":{"taskOID":40877,"originalTaskOID":40877,"setID":1435,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":7037,"questionDisplayText":"Material Requested","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of material are you interested in? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10486,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Limestone","answerDisplayText":"Limestone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10487,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Brick","answerDisplayText":"Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10488,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Sandstone","answerDisplayText":"Sandstone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10489,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Slate","answerDisplayText":"Slate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10490,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Cobblestone","answerDisplayText":"Cobblestone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10491,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Flagstone","answerDisplayText":"Flagstone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10492,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Interlocking concrete pavers","answerDisplayText":"Interlocking concrete pavers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10493,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Quartz","answerDisplayText":"Quartz","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10494,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Tiles","answerDisplayText":"Tiles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7038,"questionDisplayText":"Function","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the function?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10495,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Driveway/Parking area","answerDisplayText":"Driveway/Parking area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10496,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Interior floor","answerDisplayText":"Interior floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7039,"questionDisplayText":"Pattern","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"In what pattern is the masonry to be laid?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10497,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Length-wise","answerDisplayText":"Length-wise","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10498,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Herringbone","answerDisplayText":"Herringbone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10499,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Parquet","answerDisplayText":"Parquet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10500,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Random - irregular cut stone","answerDisplayText":"Random - irregular cut stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10501,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":7037,"questionDisplayText":"Material Requested","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of material are you interested in? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10486,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Limestone","answerDisplayText":"Limestone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10487,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Brick","answerDisplayText":"Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10488,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Sandstone","answerDisplayText":"Sandstone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10489,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Slate","answerDisplayText":"Slate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10490,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Cobblestone","answerDisplayText":"Cobblestone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10491,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Flagstone","answerDisplayText":"Flagstone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10492,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Interlocking concrete pavers","answerDisplayText":"Interlocking concrete pavers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10493,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Quartz","answerDisplayText":"Quartz","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10494,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Tiles","answerDisplayText":"Tiles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10486,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Limestone","answerDisplayText":"Limestone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10487,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Brick","answerDisplayText":"Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10488,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Sandstone","answerDisplayText":"Sandstone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10489,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Slate","answerDisplayText":"Slate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10490,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Cobblestone","answerDisplayText":"Cobblestone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10491,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Flagstone","answerDisplayText":"Flagstone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10492,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Interlocking concrete pavers","answerDisplayText":"Interlocking concrete pavers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10493,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Quartz","answerDisplayText":"Quartz","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10494,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Tiles","answerDisplayText":"Tiles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7038,"questionDisplayText":"Function","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the function?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10495,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Driveway/Parking area","answerDisplayText":"Driveway/Parking area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10496,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Interior floor","answerDisplayText":"Interior floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10495,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Driveway/Parking area","answerDisplayText":"Driveway/Parking area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10496,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Interior floor","answerDisplayText":"Interior floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7039,"questionDisplayText":"Pattern","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"In what pattern is the masonry to be laid?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10497,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Length-wise","answerDisplayText":"Length-wise","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10498,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Herringbone","answerDisplayText":"Herringbone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10499,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Parquet","answerDisplayText":"Parquet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10500,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Random - irregular cut stone","answerDisplayText":"Random - irregular cut stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10501,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10497,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Length-wise","answerDisplayText":"Length-wise","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10498,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Herringbone","answerDisplayText":"Herringbone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10499,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Parquet","answerDisplayText":"Parquet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10500,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Random - irregular cut stone","answerDisplayText":"Random - irregular cut stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10501,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"isCookielessUser":true}